shopkitson.com 2015-06-10

# ShopKitson - Privacy

Kitson is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy by adhering to five foundational principles: Notice, Choice, Access, Security, and Enforcement. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of certain information by Kitson, as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of Personal Information (defined below) that we collect when you are on our web site. This policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners, if any, share with us. This Privacy Policy only governs your use of our web site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Kitson does not own or control, or to people that Kitson does not employ or manage.

 **Children's Privacy Protection**

The Kitson web site does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 13. Kitson abides by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) requirements and Kitson does not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13.

 **Awareness**

Kitson provides this page to keep you informed of our Privacy Policy practices and of the choices you may make about the way your personal information is collected and used. A link to this policy is provided on our homepage and on the bottom of every Kitson page.

 **How We Collect Personal Information**

Kitson collects information from its web site that could be used to identify you ("Personal Information") when you contact us for information. 

Such specific information is only collected via online forms and direct communications. Any other information we collect, including but not limited to browser version and operating system, do not include details that identify you and are only used for statistical analysis.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

 **Disclosure of Personal Information**

Except as set out in this section, Kitson will not disclose your Personal Information to companies other than its strategic partners and necessary service providers, including but not limited to third party consultants who may assist Kitson from time to time. Kitosn its strategic partners, and its necessary service providers use your Personal Information in order to operate the web site and to deliver the information.

While Kitson attempts to require that the third parties described above do not use or disclose your Personal Information for any purpose other than as described in this policy, Kitson cannot guarantee their compliance with such restrictions. Kitson will otherwise only release your Personal Information to third parties in the following limited circumstances: (i) if legally required to do so under a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; (ii) if the rights or property of Kitson its affiliates, their service providers or the users of the web site are at risk; and (iii) if the personal safety of users of the web site or other members of the public are at risk.

Kitson may also use your Personal Information to generate information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted ("Aggregated Information"). Aggregated Information shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis. For example, Kitson might compile Personal Information in order to determine the percentage of users that live in a particular geographic area. Kitson may also disclose Aggregated Information to third parties. For example, Kitson might inform third parties about the number of users of the web site and the activities conducted by users while on the web site.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy the assets of similar organizations. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Kitson or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of those transferred assets.

 **Protection of Personal Information**

Kitson recognizes that your privacy is important to you and therefore we employ technical security measures that endeavor to protect information from outside threats. However, Kitson, and its service providers do not represent, warrant or guarantee that Personal Information will be protected against loss, misuse or alterations, or unauthorized access by third-parties and do not accept any liability for Personal Information submitted to them, nor for your or third parties' use or misuse of Personal Information.

With respect to Kitson's employees, access to your Personal Information is restricted to those employees who require access in order to perform their employment duties. Furthermore, all Company employees are required to abide by this Privacy Policy and are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal, for breach of its provisions.

 **Revisions to this Policy**

Kitson reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you may become aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. You should visit this page from time to time to review the then-current policy because it is binding on you. This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 12, 2010.

 **Contacting Kitson**

You can contact Kitson via e-mail to request that we update your Personal Information. If you believe that Kitson has failed to adhere to this Privacy Policy, please contact Kitson at: [customerservices@shopkitson.com](mailto:customerservices@shopkitson.com).
